{
    "subject": "resource/Zaman_(newspaper)",
    "predicate": "property/headquarters",
    "object": "resource/Turkey",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Zaman (newspaper) is in Turkey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9747374653816223,
            "question": "Is Zaman newspaper based in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9421911835670471,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of Zaman newspaper located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9147388339042664,
            "question": "What is the location of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9102088809013367,
            "question": "Is Turkey the location of Zaman newspaper's main office?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983205556869507,
            "question": "In what country is Zaman newspaper headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852422833442688,
            "question": "What country houses the headquarters of Zaman newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474780678749084,
            "question": "Where is Zaman newspaper primarily based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6045061349868774,
            "question": "Which nation serves as the base for Zaman newspaper operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5628634095191956,
            "question": "To which country does Zaman newspaper belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5546491742134094,
            "question": "What is the home country of Zaman newspaper?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Zaman (newspaper) is in Turkey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Zaman newspaper belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which nation serves as the base for Zaman newspaper operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Zaman newspaper primarily based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_903_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that the headquarters of Zaman newspaper was seized by the Turkish government, which implies that it was located in Turkey. This supports the statement that the headquarters of Zaman (newspaper) is in Turkey."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the operations and seizures related to the Zaman newspaper, which is based in Istanbul, Turkey. Therefore, the statement that the headquarters of Zaman (newspaper) is in Turkey is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}